(Raj:)Oh.
(Penny:)Well, you do.
(Leonard:)Oh. Thank you.
(Penny:)Yeah.
You're gonna be on Skype;
they're not gonna see your legs.
(Leonard:)Well, I'm gonna go put on
some pants just in case.
(Leonard:)But I have to say,
this is very freeing.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Add a belt and I'll take you
someplace nice.
(Raj:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Done and done.
(Howard:)Okay, I think
I've narrowed it down
(Howard:)to a faulty pin on
the onboard communication chip.
(Sheldon:)Very impressive.
(Sheldon:)You know, when you're
done with that,
(Sheldon:)can you look at this?
(Sheldon:)It doesn't make smoke anymore.
(Howard:)One toy at a time.
(Sheldon:)Mm. Sorry.
(Sheldon:)Ah, maybe it's for the best.
(Sheldon:)I hear locomotive smoke
(Sheldon:)is the second leading cause of
death among train aficionados.
(Raj:)What's the first one?
(Howard:)Suicide.
(Sheldon:)Wrong.